Michelson, Vera. P.; Papers apap379
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1921-2018; Undated; 4; 1.5 cubic ft.
  - Ivy, Donald "Dontay", 1976; 2014-2016; Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - La Court, Charles Jr. Paper, 2002-2013; Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Law Enforcement Engagement, 2008; 2015-2018; Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - "Malcolm X: The Man and His Ideas" Booklet, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Mothers in Charge, 2007; 2011; 2013-2015; Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - New Research on Malcolm X #9 Tape 1: Sayles Hook - Cone, Undated (Cassette 64)
  - New York State Bail Reform, 2017-2018; Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - "Palestinians and the PLO" Booklet, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Police Misconduct, 1985-1995; Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Police Misconduct (1 of 2), 1998-2017; Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Police Misconduct (1 of 2), 1998-2017; Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Project Vote, Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Publications of Green, Alice, 2004; 2012-2013; 2018; Undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Racial Profiling, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Reproductive Health Handouts, 2006; Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Rucker, Ronnie Papers, 1996-1997; 1999 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Script to Street: Opioids and The Law in the Capital District, 2017 March 3 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - See Us, Support Us, 2017 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Sheehan's Transition Team Recommendations, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Simpson, Merton, 2017 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Smith, Barbara Papers, 2002-2011; Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Smith, Damu, 2003-2006; Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Socialism/Communism Booklets (1 of 2), 1935-1989; Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Socialism/Communism Booklets (2 of 2), 1935-1989; Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Tasing, 2011-2012; 2014-2015; Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Telephone Talk: PLO/Mid East, Undated (Cassette 65)
  - Theoretical Perspectives on Malcolm X #2 Tape 2, Undated (Cassette 66)
  - Trauma Initiative Personal Notes, 2015-2018 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Youth Culture and Rebellion #12 Tape 1, 2, Undated (Cassette 67)